

ABOUT ME -

"Hello, my name is Elifissa Virgill Anak Dimbap. I'm a fresh graduate from Bachelor of Information Science (Hons) Records Management. However, I have few working experiences. Take your time, check my resume, see my skills, some of my work, my experience, and when you are ready drop me a message."

CONTACT ME



No. 5545, Lot 5151 (SL16), Lorong Samarindah 29D3, Jalan Datuk Mohd Musa, 94300 Kota Samarahan, Kuching Sarawak.



016 885 0073



elifissavirgill91@gmail.com

EXPERTISE

- Data Entry
- Filing And Records Management
- Public Relation
- Clerical

LANGUAGES

- Bahasa Melayu
- **English**
- Mandarin



PERSONAL SKILLS

SELF MOTIVATED

ORGANIZATION

TEAM PLAY

TRAINING

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MS OFFICE

PHOTOSHOP

MACROMEDIA DIRECTOR

INTERNET



BACHELOR IN INFORMATION SCIENCE (HONS) RECORDS MANAGEMENT

Universiti Teknologi MARA (2014 - 2017)

CGPA: 3.50

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION MANAGEMENT

Universiti Teknologi MARA (2011 - 2014)

CGPA: 3.15

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA (SPM)

SMK KALAKA ROBAN (2004 - 2008)2A, 1B, 2C, 3D



EXPERIENCE

DOCUMENT CONTROLLER PRACTICAL STUDENT UNIT PEMANTAUAN PELAKSANAAN NEGERI, JABATAN KETUA MENTERI/ KUCHING/ AUGUST 2016 **DECEMBER 2016**

I undergone my internship for five months here. During the training, I have digitizing incoming mail and uploading the mail into the electronic records system for data entry purpose, doing some administrative work, acted as the intermediary between the officers and the officers from other agencies.

ADMINISTRATIVE CLERK **MARKETING** cum **ASSISTANT**

SMH MEMORIAL SARATOK SDN BHD/ SARATOK/ JULY 2014 - AUGUST 2014

I worked here after finish my diploma and quit job to pursue my degree. I have preparing purchase order and invoice, data entry, answering phone call, dealing with customers regarding the product payment, organizing event for product launch and do few promotional jobs.

CASHIER AND SHOP ASSISTANT SYARIKAT CAHAYA KEMBANG MELATI/ ROBAN/ 2009 -2011

This is a grocery store. I work here after SPM. I have worked as cashier as well as shop assistant here. I also received the stocks from the supplier and manage the payment. I also some clerical task like record keeping and handling the incoming invoice, delivery order and receipt.



AWARD

DEAN LIST AWARD:

- SEMESTER 4 (2015)
- SEMESTER 6 (2016)
- **SEMESTER 7 (2017)**



REFERENCES

Dr Ezza Rafedziawati Bt. Kamal Rafedzi Senior Lecturer. **UiTM Kampus Puncak** Perdana. Jalan Pulau Angsa AU10/A Shah Alam 40150 Selangor 03-79622307

Raya Aida Bt. Abdul Karim Assistant Director, Unit Pemantauan Pelaksanaan Negeri, Tingkat 5, Wisma Bapa Malaysia, Petra Java, 93502 Kuching, Sarawak. 01139260540